trollfootball.me 2019-11-27

# Privacy Policy - Troll Football

At Troll Football, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Troll Football and how it is used.

**Personal Information:** Although we request the use of your details (username / email), we just use the information for authentication and verification purposes and the information is never shared or leaked to any organisation nor Troll Football will e-mail you regarding asking for any payment, or asking for any passwords. We would never send any promotional emails. **We respect your privacy**

**Log Files :** We log the errors / hack attempts / suspicious actions. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable and to conclude logging of these files is important for analyzing malicious users and keeping them at bay, ensuring maximum availability of Troll Football

**Cookies :** Troll Football uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific informations via which we customize Web page content.

Also note that our advertising partners **may** use cookies on our site.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks might use the cookies for serving advertisements and links that appear on Troll Football. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

**Troll Football has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.Troll Football's privacy policy does not apply to them and we cannot control the activities of other advertisers or providers.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

Enjoy your time at Troll Football

Team Troll Football

We use cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website Details OK, Got it 

### We make use of cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific informations via which we customize Web page content.However, none of this cookies / data would be used to identify or contact you in person.

* * *

To disable all cookies through the browser, click on the corresponding icon and follow the instructions: 

  1. Chrome: [Disable Cookies](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416?hl=en) 
  2. Firefox: [Disable Cookies](https://support.mozilla.org/en-GB/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences) 
  3. Internet Explorer: [Disable Cookies](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-gb/internet-explorer/delete-manage-cookies#ie=ie-11) 
  4. Opera: [Disable Cookies](http://help.opera.com/Windows/10.00/en/cookies.html) 
  5. Safari: [Disable Cookies](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH17191?viewlocale=en_GB)
